<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Talabat online payment</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Online Payment Annexure</subject>
    <textOnly>ADDITIONAL PAYMENT METHODS

Restaurant Name ………………………………..

Manager Name ………………………………..

Contact # ………………………………..


Dear Sir/Madam,

We will be launching the Debit/Credit Card online payment service on Talabat.com and Foodonclick.com platforms based on the increased demand from our customers to enable this payment method on our platforms.


Kindly note the bank charge rate for this service is (2%) from the total order amount.


The Bank fees for the Debit /Credit Card online payment service will be paid directly by Talabat &amp; Foodonclick till 31/12/2015. The bank fees will be transferred to the subscribed partner restaurant after this date.

You can subscribe to this service by filling and signing this form. Kindly return this form to the Fax or Email information highlighted below.

Note 1: Filling this form will be considered an official approval for subscribing to the (Debit / Credit Card) online payment method. The service will be automatically activated for your restaurant upon launching the service.

Note 2: Debit/Credit card online transactions value will be deposited directly to Talabat and Foodonclick bank accounts. The transactions amount will be transferred to your respective restaurant within (7) working days from the end of each month.

Name:

Signature:

Date:


Please sign and return it to

Fax:

E-mail:



طريقة سداد إضافية

اسم المطعم:................................................

اسم المدير:.................................................

رقم الاتصال:...............................................


السادة الأفاضل

يسعدنا أن نُعلن أننا بصدد البدأ في إطلاق خدمة السداد عن طريق بطاقات الإئتمان/الدّين على موقع وتطبيقات طلبات و فود أون كليك، وذلك تلبية للطلب المتنامي من عملائنا لتوفير تلك الخدمة.




علما بأن العمولة البنكية المستحقة هي نسبة (2%) من إجمالي قيمة الطلب.


لن يتم تطبيق الرسوم البنكية على المطاعم المشتركة في الخدمة حتى تاريخ 31/12/2015، وأنه سيتم سداد هذه الرسوم البنكية مباشرة من قبل شركتي طلبات و فود أون كليك وسيتم تحميل الرسوم البنكية على المطاعم المشتركة في تلك الخدمة بعد التاريخ المذكور أعلاه.



بإمكانكم الإشتراك في تلك الخدمة بملئ وتوقيع هذا النموذج وأرساله لنا عن طريق الفاكس او البريد الإلكتروني.


ملاحظة 1: تعبئة هذا النموذج تعتبر موافقة رسمية للإشتراك في تلك الخدمة وسوف يتم تفعيل طريقة السداد الجديدة (بطاقات الأئتمان/ الدّين) لمطعكم عند إطلاق هذه الخدمة.


ملاحظة 2: سوف يتم تحويل قيمة عمليات السداد عن طريق بطاقات الإئتمان /الدّين إلى الحساب المصرفي لشركة طلبات و فود أون كليك ، ثم يتم تحويلها إلى حسابكم خلال (7) أيام عمل من نهاية كل شهر.

الإسم:

التوقيع :

التاريخ:

برجاء التوقيع وإرسال النموذج إلينا عن طريق

فاكس:

البريد الإلكتروني:</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
