<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <attachedDocuments>DH_AU_Menu_Samples/Menu_Sample_Generic2.pdf</attachedDocuments>
    <attachedDocuments>DH_AU_Menu_Samples/Menu_Sample_Indian.pdf</attachedDocuments>
    <attachedDocuments>DH_AU_Menu_Samples/Menu_Sample_Thai2A.pdf</attachedDocuments>
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>DH_AU_Letterhead</letterhead>
    <name>DH AU Confirmation – Menu Printing (NSD Print)</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>Menu Printing Confirmation {!Account.Restaurant_Name__c}</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Contact.FirstName},

Please find attached a letter confirming your interest to order menus with Delivery Hero. The next steps required to finalise your menu printing are as follows:

1. Choose a design for your new menu and advise us of your selection. You can choose to use:
1) your existing menu*; or
2) one of the available templates from NSD Print.
*If you would like to use your existing menu design, please note that small layout changes may be required to make space for the Delivery Hero voucher and banners.

2. Please email the following information to us within 48 hours:
- your current menu (in high resolution PDF where possible)
- your logo in high resolution
- all required changes for your new menu

3. Our printing partner NSD Print will contact you within 24 hours to take your payment details and process the order. Payment can be made via bank transfer or VISA/Mastercard and is processed in two stages:
1) a non‐refundable $90 (excl. GST) deposit will be charged by NSD Print on initial order confirmation; and
2) the balance of payment, being the Invoice Total per the attached letter less the deposit paid, will be charged by NSD Print upon approval of final artwork for printing

If you have any questions please do not hesitate to contact either NSD Print or ourselves. We’ve also included a menu distribution contact below as an optional recommendation.

Thank you!

Sincerely,
Your Delivery Hero Team.
{!User.Name}
{!User.Phone}
{!User.Email}

Menu Printing Contact:
Sales Team NSD Print Management
Postal Address: PO Box 940 St Ives, NSW 2075
Office Address: Suite 1.28, Level 2, 802-808 Pacific Highway, Gordon 2072
Phone: (02) 9440 1577
Fax: (02) 9440 1688
Email: dh@nsdprint.com.au

(Optional) Menu Distribution Contact:
LetterboxPush
Craig Morris
Phone: 1300 436 806
Email: letterboxpush@parcelpush.com.au
Website: www.letterboxpush.com.au
10,000:  $495 (plus GST) = $49.50/1,000 (plus GST)
20,000:  $990 (plus GST) = $49.50/1,000 (plus GST)
40,000:  $1,780 (plus GST) = $44.50/1,000 (plus GST)
Note: For all areas outside the Capital City 20km radius, a separate competitive quote will be provided.</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
